http://www.unidroit.org/cookie-policy

SECURED TRANSACTIONS
Search ...
NEWS AND EVENTSABOUT UNIDROITOverviewMembershipWork ProgrammeInstitutional DocumentsStatuteRegulationsHeadquarters AgreementGoverning CouncilSecretariatMEETINGSGeneral AssemblyGoverning CouncilFinance CommitteeStudies / ImplementationWORK IN PROGRESSAgricultural land investmentBest Practice Effective EnforcementDigital Assets and Private LawFactoring Model LawMAC PrepComModel Law on Warehouse ReceiptsPrivate Art CollectionsRail PrepComSpace PrepComTransnational Civil ProcedureINSTRUMENTSAgencyCapital MarketsGeneva ConventionLegislative GuideNettingCivil ProcedureALI/UNIDROIT PrinciplesELI/UNIDROIT RulesCommercial ContractsTripartite Legal GuideUNIDROIT Principles 2016UNIDROIT Principles 2010UNIDROIT Principles 2004UNIDROIT Principles 1994UPICC Model ClausesContract FarmingLegal GuideCultural Property1995 ConventionModel ProvisionsFactoringFranchisingModel LawGuideFirst Edition 1998Second Edition 2007International SalesULIS 1964ULFC 1964International WillLeasingConventionModel LawReinsurance ContractsSecurity InterestsCape Town ConventionAircraft ProtocolRail ProtocolSpace ProtocolMAC ProtocolTransportCCVCMRSTUDIES-> by classification-> by numberArbitrationBanking LawCapital marketsCivil liabilityCivil procedureCompany lawContract FarmingContracts (in general)Cultural propertyFactoringFranchisingForwarding
agencyHotelkeepersInsuranceIntellectual propertyInternational sales lawLeasingLegal aspects of social businessLegal Status of WomenMaintenance obligationsMethodologyMovement of personsNatural resourcesNegotiable instrumentsNon-legislative activitiesSecurity InterestsPaymentsPrivate Law and Agric. Develop.Transport lawTravel agenciesTrustUnfair competitionWillsLIBRARYOverviewAccess and hoursLibrary rulesScholarships programmeGorla CollectionHistoryCatalogueOnline CataloguePUBLICATIONSUNIDROIT PublicationsUniform Law ReviewRESEARCH AND INTERNSHIPS
Privacy and Cookie PolicyLast Updated: 15 September 2015 |
Print	 |
Email
Privacy and Cookie Policy
UNIDROIT is aware that the protection of personal data and its confidential handling is of great concern to our users. We would, therefore, like to illustrate which information we collect and how we handle it, According to the Italian Data Protection Code (Legislative Decree no. 196 of 30 June 2003) and the the "Simplified Arrangements to Provide Information and Obtain Consent Regarding Cookies" issued by the Italian Data Protection Authority (8 may 2014).
Privacy Policy and consent to data processing
In compliance with the duty to inform set forth under art. 13 of the Italian Legislative Decree n.196, 30 June 2003, “Italian Personal Data Protection Code”, we inform you that the personal data supplied by you to us through the voluntary and optional submission of the contact form will be collected, stored and processed by our company in accordance with the above-mentioned law, only for the purpose of providing you with the service required.
Furthermore, we want to inform you that should you not consent to the collection, storage and processing of the data supplied, you will not be able to access the service you requested.
The collection and processing of the personal data supplied by you to us will be performed by our staff appointed to this duty by the means of manual and IT tools, in ways suitable to protect the security and confidentiality of the data.
The data supplied will be stored only for the period of time necessary to fulfil the purposes mentioned above. Nonetheless, pursuant to Art. 7 of the Decree mentioned above, you have the opportunity to exercise your rights as specified in the Article, such as to request a free update, the correction, removal or integration of your personal data. Should you wish to do this, please write to us to the following email address: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Data controller (*)
UNIDROIT designated data controller: Ms Lena Peters.
(*) According to Italian Data Protection Code, data controller is the natural person, company, association or other entity actually in control of the processing of personal data and empowered to take the essential decisions on the purposes and mechanisms of such processing, including the applicable security measures.
Cookie Policy
To make our website easier and more enjoyable to use, we use cookies throughout the site. Cookies are little pieces of data that allow us to compare new and past visitors, understand how users navigate through our site and provide us with data that we can use to make the experience more enjoyable and more effective in the future. Cookies do not log any personal information about a user, and identifiable data is never stored. If you would like to avoid the use of cookies, you must tailor your computer settings to erase all website Cookies and/or to notify you via a warning if cookies are being stored. To proceed without changes to the cookie implementation, simply continue browsing our website.
If you need further assistance, please visit the following links for more information on how to control or delete cookies in the main web browsers:
Chrome
Mozilla Firefox
Apple Safari
Windows Internet Explorer
The types of cookie we use are strictly necessary cookies
These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies, services you have asked for (like information request forms etc.) cannot be provided.
These cookies also allow the website to remember choices you make (such as the language) and provide enhanced, more personal features. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting a blog post. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and cookies cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
Below you can find a list of the strictly necessary cookies we use on our website.
Textpattern cookies
We use a CMS (Content Management System), Textpattern, to publish and manage the content on our website. Textpattern uses cookies to collect information (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you do not have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. For non-registered users: all the information we collect is completely anonymous. For registered users (staff, contributors, webmaster) we only collect those details that are strictly necessary to allow them to perform their duties (i.e. publish articles, website maintenance).
- l10n_admin_long_lang, l10n_admin_short_lang, l10n_long_lang, l10n_request_uri, l10n_short_lang- these cookies collect information about language choice, and allow to switch language and keep your choice consistent throughout the website;
- txp_login, txp_login_public- only used for registered users, these cookies keep track of login details;
- ee_anon- only used for registered users, these cookies set preferences about users' anonymity.
You can control or delete these cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser.
Other necessary cookies
The following cookies are used to store your preferences about cookies on this website:
- cc_analytics, cc_necessary, cookiescriptaccept
Analytics cookies
These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance, which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies do not collect information that could be used to identify a visitor. These cookies collect only aggregated, anonymous data, which is only used to improve how a website works. This information is collected using the following cookies, provided by a third party tool, Google Analytics:
- __utma -  Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics;
- __utmb -   Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
- __utmc -  Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
- __utmz -  Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached the site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics;
- _ga -  Used to distinguish users.
Data Privacy Statement for Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your anonymised IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
You can prevent Google from detecting a cookie that is generated because of and related to your usage of this website (including your IP address) as well as processing of this data by downloading and installing this browser plugin: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
Third party cookies
Our site, like most websites, includes functionality provided by third parties.
YouTubeThis website uses YouTube to serve embedded videos to our users. YouTube uses the following cookies to allow you to view and share content: - ACTIVITY, GEUP, PREF, VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, YSC, __utma,__utmc, __utmz, _ga, uploader
For further details on the cookies set by YouTube, please refer to the YouTube website.
Other third party services
Please note that third party services like Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and Flickr may set cookies for sharing content on social networks or for producing access statistics. The presence, number and status of cookies may depend on how you use the platforms concerned before or while visiting our website. The privacy implications of this will vary from social network to social network and will be dependent on the privacy settings you have chosen on these networks. We do not control the setting of third-party cookies; although we try to keep this information up to date, these third-party services may set cookies in addition to those listed above.
By using our website, you agree that we can place the above-mentioned cookies on your device
By using unidroit.org you agree to our use of cookies to enhance your experience.     I understand   Know more
